A Guide to the Virginia Department of Treasury, Division of Unclaimed Property, 1822-1991
Library of Virginia
- Records - Accession 31473, 1830-1962., Extent: 22 boxes. (Box 1-22)
  - Lot 689 - Thomas E. Bass Papers,1906-1921. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Lot 690 - Deeds,1880-1883. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Lot 691 - Butler Family Papers,1918-1928. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Lot 692 - Campas Family Papers,1916-1932. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Lot 694 - Margaret K. Cassidy Papers,1919-1920. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Lot 695 - Woodson C. Cobb Papers, Contracts,1894-1908. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Lot 695 - Woodson C. Cobb Papers, Correspondence,1900-1911. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Lot 695 - Woodson C. Cobb Papers, Miscellaneous,1895-1911. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Lot 697 - Dillinger Family Papers,1934-1947. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Lot 698 - Mary C. Dixon Papers,1896-1927. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Lot 699 - W.G. Cornell Company Papers,1886-1925. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Lot 700 - Tax Receipts,1920. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Lot 701 - Norman Crawford Papers,1927-1928. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Lot 702 - Mamie G. Cromwell Papers,1919-1925. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Lot 704 - R. L. Davis Papers,1918-1921. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Lot 708 - Bill of Sale,1934. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Lot 709 - Myrtle L. Strong & Ella M. Dozier Papers,1924-1928. (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Lot 712 - Insurance Policy,1919-1920. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Lot 714 - Leoda P. Etheridge Papers,1932-1950. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Lot 715 - Agnes I. Fields Papers. (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Lot 716 - J. M. Feear Letters,1921-1923. (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Lot 717 - Irving Frost Papers,1922-1924. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Lot 718 - Durward Fry Card,1943. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Lot 719 - A. C. Gardman Papers,1912-1922. (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Lot 721 - Joseph J. Gottlieb Papers,1940-1941. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Lot 722 - Jewell P. Hankins Papers,1925. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Lot 724 - Insurance Policies,1925. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Lot 725 - Floyd Hurst Papers,1919-1926. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Lot 726 - Insurance Policies,1940-1941. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Lot 728 - Alida Wilson Jones Papers,1899-1908. (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Lot 730 - Mary S. Kalesta Papers,1943-1946. (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Lot 731 - Pamphlet,1931. (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Lot 732 - Insurance Policy,1919. (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Lot 733 - Agreement,1924. (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Lot 735 - Harry Byer LaFavre Papers,1952-1953. (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Lot 736 - Letter,1946. (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Lots 737-738 - Louis S. Greenblatt Papers,1908-1937. (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Lot 739 - Orvia Evert Grossnickle Papers,1917-1918. (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Lot 741 - Carrie M. Hall Papers,1884-1929. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Lot 744 - George William Land Papers,1912-1923. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Lot 745 - Undean Larsen Papers. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Lot 750 - Insurance Policies,1948. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Lot 751 - Norfolk Truckers Exchange Records,1915-1927. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Lot 752 - Contract,1942. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Lot 753 - Insurance Policy,1926. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Lot 753 - Insurance Policy,1926. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Lot 754 - Insurance Policies,1931-1932. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Lot 755 - George W. Moores Papers,1928-1936. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Lot 757 - R. E. Morris Papers,1919-1920. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Lot 758 - William L. Morrisette Papers,1905-1931. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Lot 759 - James G. Mould Papers,1932. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Lot 760 - Henry V. Murick Papers,1921-1927. (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Lot 768 - Agreements,1932. (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Lot 769 - George W. Richardson Papers,1922-1927. (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Lot 772 - Arthur L. Roberts Papers,1908-1946. (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Lot 773 - Howard E. Robinson Indenture,1931. (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Lot 774 - Certificate,1917. (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Lot 775 - William A. Rogers Papers,1924-1931. (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Lot 776 - Leona Rosenbaum Papers,1929-1932. (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Lot 777 - Insurance Policies,1948. (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Lot 778 - Ow Chuck Sam Papers,1944-1948. (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Lot 779 - Insurance Policy,1925. (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Lot 780 - Insurance Policy,1945. (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Lot 781 - Max Schachman Papers,1940-1946. (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Lot 782 - Insurance Policies,1919. (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Lot 783 - Insurance Policies,1932-1933. (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Lot 784 - Grace Lovelace Sessoms Papers,1923-1925. (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Lot 785 - Henry and Maude Shannon Papers,1903-1937. (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Lot 786 - Depositions,1920. (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Lot 787 - Deeds,1912-1915. (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Lot 790 - Deed,1929. (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Lot 791 - R. N. Strange Papers,1920. (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Lot 793 - Harry Crawford Taylor Papers,1942-1943. (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Lot 794 - Richard B. Taylor Papers,1899-1901. (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Lot 795 - Hanna Thomas Papers,1936-1949. (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Lot 795a - Hanna R. Thomas Papers,1949. (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Lot 796 - War Risk Insurance,1917. (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Lot 798 - Fire Insurance Policy and Title Survey,1954. (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Lot 799 - Deed,1944. (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Lot 802 - Birth certificate,1924. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Lot 804 - Walter Family Papers,1935-1936. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Lot 805 - Will,1917. (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Lot 808 - Insurance Policies,1921-1923. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Lot 809 - Insurance Records,1942-1943. (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Lot 815 - Bond Coupons,1933-1935. (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Lot 819 - Birth Records,1951. (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Lot 820 - Military Order and Marriage Records,1939-1944. (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Lot 821 - Huggett Family Papers,1942-1945. (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Lot 822 - Sales Contract and Insurance Policies,1943-1946. (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Lot 825 - Deed and Agreement,1931. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Lot 826 - Deed, Plat and Lease,1946-1948. (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Lot 828 - Business Papers,1946-1948. (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Lot 829 - Fire Insurance Policies,1947. (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Lot 830 - John W. Shackleford Jr. Papers,1920-1950. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Lot 837 - George T. Dudley Estate Papers,1920-1950. (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Lot 844 - Agreeemnt,1955. (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Lot 845 - Insurance Policy, Abstract of Title, Deed, Contract,1918-1923. (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Lot 847 - Letters,1940-1941. (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Lot 848 - Letter, Military Record, and Handkerchief,1911-1923. (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Lot 850 - Deeds,1937-1938. (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Lot 851 - Miscellaneous Letters,1937-1938. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Lot 853 - Contact and Insurance Policies,1951. (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Lot 854 - Fire Insurance Policies,1952. (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Lot 855 - Jones Family Papers,1924-1927. (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Lot 857 - Willard H. Simmons Papers,1937-1943. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Lot 858 - Ward Family Papers,1943-1945. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Lot 862 - Fire Insurance Policy,1953. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Lot 863 - Deed and Plat,1950. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Lot 865 - Murray Family Papers,1943-953. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Lot 865 - Sweeney Family Papers,1948-1953. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Lot 866 - Willis-Blankenship Papers,1949-1953. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Lot 867 - Deeds,1955-1957. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Lot 868 - Will,1946. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Lot 869 - Deed, Plat, and Separation Notice,1956. (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Lot 872 - Rebecca R. Paxton Papers,1922-1949. (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Lot 873 - Miscellaneous Papers,1940-1943. (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Lot 874 - Fire Insurance Policy,1945. (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Lot 876 - Deed, Title, Plat, Lease, and Photographs,1944-1949. (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Lot 877 - Fields-Vinson Papers,1938-1954. (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Lot 879 - Partnership Papers, Power of Attorney, and Insurance Policy,1940-1944. (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Lot 880 - Grant of Immunity,1953. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Lot 882 - Birth and Marraige Records,1934-1953. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Lot 884 - Yates Family Papers,1937-1944. (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Lot 888 - Dudley Family Papers,1913-1934. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Lot 888 - Dudley Family Papers,1913-1934. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Lot 888 - Dudley Family Papers,1913-1934. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Lot 890 - Miscellaneous Records,1941. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Lot 891 - Letters,1943. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Lot 892 - Agreements and Reports,1943. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Lot 893 - Allen E. Davis Papers,1942-1943. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Lot 894 - Birth Certificate,1943. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Lot 895 - Miller-Waldrop Papers,1929-1936. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Lot 897 - Marriage Certificate and Correspondence,1945-1947. (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Lot 899 - Will,1945. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Lot 900 - Certificate,1946. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Lot 901 - Lease and Insurance Policies,1941-1945. (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Lot 902 - Correspondence,1945. (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Lot 904 - Certificate,1950. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Lot 906 - Will and Insurance Policy,1954-1955. (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Lot 914 - Mullins Family Papers,1939-1959. (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Lot 915 - Neff Family Papers,1842-1915. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Lot 916 - Birth Record,1962. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Lot 917 - Citizenship Papers,1904. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Lot 919 - George E. King Papers,1955-1956. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Lot 920 - William A. Price Papers,1943. (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Lot 922 - Wilber W. Westbrook Jr Papers,1952-1955. (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Lot 923 - John C. Howell Papers,1940-1946. (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Lot 924 - Johnston Family Papers,1931-1948. (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Lot 925 - Deeds, Leases, Contracts, and Agreeements,1946-1948. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Lot 927 - Deeds,1948. (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Lot 1026 - Will,1935. (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Lot 1027 - Will,1931. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Lot 1028 - Deed and Plat,1924. (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Lot 1039 - Basil J. Frazier Papers,1948-1950. (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Lot 1041 - Marriage Certificate and Fire Insurance Policy,1926-1947. (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Lot 208 - Coastwise Dredging Company. (Box 21, Folder 1)
    Oversized.
  - Lot 220 - Insurance Policies,1836-1854. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Lot 392 - St. John Family Papers. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Lot 453 - Archibald Grant Papers. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Lot 576 - Life Insurance Certificate,1922. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Lot 596 - Pulley Family Papers,1918-1947. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Lot 598 - Deed and Map,1910. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Lot 682 - Oliver S. Ackiss Papers. (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Accession 32981,1883-1931., Extent: 4 boxes, 2 volumes. (Box 22-24)
  Consists of the M. F. W. Speers and W. A. Thomas Papers.
  - Lot 28/899 - W. A. Thomas Papers,. (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Lot 28/899 - M. W. F. Speers Papers. (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Lot 28/899 - M. W. F. Speers Papers. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Lot 28/899 - M. W. F. Speers Papers. (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Lot 28/899 - M. W. F. Speers Papers. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Lot 28/899 - M. W. F. Speers Papers. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Lot 28/899 - M. W. F. Speers Papers. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Lot 28/899 - M. W. F. Speers Papers. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Lot 28/899 - M. W. F. Speers Papers. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Lot 28/899 - M. W. F. Speers Papers. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Lot 28/899 - M. W. F. Speers Papers. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Lot 28/899 - W. A. Thomas Papers-Accoumt Books,1889. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Lot 28/899 - W. A. Thomas Papers-Checks and Receipts,1883-1889. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Lot 28/899 - W. A. Thomas Papers-Inventory Book,1889. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - W. A. Thomas Papers-Journal and Cash Book,1889.
  - W. A. Thomas Papers-Ledger,1889.
- Accession 42943,1822-1978., Extent: 10 boxes. (Box 25-34)
  - Lot 6543 - Personal Papers of Clara N. Lucas,1917-1925. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Lot 6766 - Personal Papers of the Hathaway Family,1976. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Lot 6767 - Personal Papers of Louis E. Chappell,1966-1970. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Lot 6769 - Personal Papers of the Barnes Family,1965-1967. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Lot 6773 - Personal Papers of Catherine Burkett,1955. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Lot 6775 - Personal Papers of Roxanne Michelle Moore,1952-1976. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Lot 6776 - Personal Papers of Robert P. Druck,1970. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Lot 6780 - Personal Papers of Sheryl S. Reilly,1977. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Lot 6782 - Personal Papers of Bruce R. Pray,1967. (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Lot 6784 - Personal Papers of John G. Burdette,1964-1975. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Lot 6786 - Personal Papers of Helen A. Goff,ca. 1965. (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Lot 6787 - Personal Papers of Jean Waters Wainio,1972. (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Lot 6788 - Personal Papers of the Trapkin Family,1978. (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Lot 6789 - Personal Papers of Eileen Hagan,1968. (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Lot 6791 - Personal Papers of Frank McGourty,1937-1970. (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Lot 6792 - Personal Papers of Ronald F. Kornell,1935-1976. (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Lot 6796 - Personal Papers of R. W. Messick,1913-1914. (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Lot 6797 - Personal Papers of Jacqueline S. Novak,1967. (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Lot 6798 - Personal Papers of Kenneth Hill,1974. (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Lot 6804 - Personal Papers of the DeWeese Family,1918-1974. (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Lot 6805 - Personal Papers of Dorothy L. Stadler,1973. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Lot 6806 - Personal Papers of John W. Anderson,1966. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Lot 6810 - Personal Papers of Stanley Metcalfe,1952-1969. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Lot 6811 - Personal Papers of Mary Frances Elliott,1956-1959. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Lot 8743 - Personal Papers of Dorothy M. Hughes,1961. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Lot 20697 - Personal Papers of James T. Rogers,1965-1973. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Lot 22544 - Personal Papers of Faye Humphries,1949-1955. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Lot 25538 - Personal Papers of Tildsley G. Graham,1906-1922. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Lot 38726 - Personal Papers of Daniel J. Ragen, Jr.,1934-1939. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Lot 39268 - Papers of the Richmond Tomato Repacking Company,1949. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Lot 39861 - Personal Papers of W. C. Griffin,1919-1923. (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Lot 43494 - Personal Papers of Josephine D. Church,1956-1959. (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Lot 46148 - Personal Papers of Howard L. Johnson,1943-1962. (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Lot 47804 - Personal Papers of Beulah Brumfield Carter,1963. (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Lot 51015 - Personal Papers of James W. Farr,1972. (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Lot 69720 - Personal Papers of Webster D. Pulliam Jr.,1949-1973. (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Lot 70810 - Personal Papers of Annabel M. Doane,1931-1947. (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Lot 71815 - Personal Papers of J. R. Lassiter,1925. (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Lot 76263 - Personal Papers of J. C. Ferrell,1914. (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Lot 80472 - Personal Papers of Melva A. Coughey,1946-1953. (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Lot 81031 - Personal Papers of William E. Snowden,1898-1924. (1 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Lot 81031 - Personal Papers of William E. Snowden,1898-1924. (2 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Lot 110719 - Personal Papers of James W. Small,1975. (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Lot 110893 - Personal Papers of Ruth E. Bristol Phelps,. (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Lot 120160 - Personal Papers of John S. Thomas,1921. (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Lot 130082 - Papers of the Landes Family,1944-1945. (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Lot 146717 - Personal Papers of Earl S. Holland,1912-1966. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Lot 154911 - Personal Papers of Phillip W. Stinchfield,1926. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Lot 170965 - Personal Papers of Henry T. C. Colonna,1949-1964. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Lot 171951 - Personal Papers of William A. Pace,1927-1930. (1 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Lot 171951 - Personal Papers of William A. Pace,1927-1930. (2 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Lot 176482 - Personal Papers of John O. Crider,1911-1924. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Lot 189149 - Personal Papers of Ernest Lee,1954-1969. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Lot 194056 - Personal Papers of Gustaf A. Anderson,1953. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Lot 197100 - Personal Papers of the Wiggins Family,1966. (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Lot 201083 - Personal Papers of Sam W. Turner,1949-1955. (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Lot 210056 - Personal Papers of Alex M. Jones,1919. (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Lot 214799 - Personal Papers of Virginia Hughes,1929-1958. (1 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Lot 214799 - Personal Papers of Virginia Hughes,1929-1958. (2 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Lot 219847 - Personal Papers of Newton S. Foster,1916. (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Lot 244699 - Personal Papers of Thomas C. Johnson,1952-1957. (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Lot 254817 - Personal Papers of Edd Riddick,1906. (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Lot 256792 - Personal Papers of Percy W. Leland,1955-1957. (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Lot 257361 - Personal Papers of Marlin B. Waymack,1952-1954. (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Lot 261036 - Personal Papers of J. W. Lytton,1917-1921. (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Lot 301174 - Personal Papers of David W. McDaniels,1962-1964. (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Lot 310926 - Personal Papers of Francis R. Collins,1966. (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Lot 320634 - Personal Papers of Alvin R. Pruitt,1963. (Box 27, Folder 22)
  - Lot 321428 - Personal Papers of Dollie W. Hankins,1967. (Box 27, Folder 23)
  - Lot 321652 - Personal Papers of John R. Patrick,. (1 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 24)
  - Lot 321652 - Personal Papers of John R. Patrick,. (2 of 2) (Box 27, Folder 25)
  - Lot 331358 - Personal Papers of the Lee Family,1969-1970. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Lot 350355 - Personal Papers of John S. Novinger,1968-1969. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Lot 352005 - Personal Papers of Mary Lee Fleming,1938-1956. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Lot 387423 - Personal Papers of Ralston M. McInnis, Sr,1966. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Lot 387804 - Personal Papers of Frances A. Moore,1937-1953. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Lot 395665 - Personal Papers of Charles L. Hickman,1947-1951. (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Lot 398732 - Personal Papers of Douglas Bell,1915. (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Lot 401164 - Personal Papers of Jack M. Collins,1967. (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Lot 406524 - Personal Papers of James Ferguson,1967. (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Lot 411025 - Personal Papers of Ellis C. White,1924-1926. (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Lot 438741 - Personal Papers of Leon Probert,1955-1956. (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Lot 444759 - Personal Papers of the Uzzle Family,1948. (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Lot 459656 - Personal Papers of William A. Shelton,1941. (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Lot 469093 - Personal Papers of Jacob Whitmer,1944. (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Lot 475238 - Personal Papers of John W. Reynolds,1918. (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Lot 500258 - Personal Papers of Jean A. Robinette,1959-1971. (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Lot 509846 - Personal Papers of B. G. Paulin,1918-1924. (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Lot 521672 - Personal Papers of Nick Lee,1968. (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Lot 535478 - Personal Papers of A. W. Zgonc,1961. (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Lot 551427 - Personal Papers of Walter F. Howe,1946-1950. (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Lot 554827 - Personal Papers of Aaron and Madge Cohen,1941-1947. (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Lot 554842 - Personal Papers of J. Fenton Matthews,1940-1947. (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Lot 556959 - Personal Papers of Florence E. Nock,1928-1934. (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Lot 575615 - Personal Papers of John N. Williams,1888-1907. (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Lot 575659 - Personal Papers of Ellis Walter, Jr,1959. (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Lot 577571 - Personal Papers of Eloise W. Holloman,1972. (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Lot 596621 - Personal Papers of Gerald Luck,1919-1933. (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Lot 600205 - Personal Papers of Louis I. Rudd,1940-1953. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Lot 601991 - Personal Papers of J. E. Jones,1935-1938. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Lot 604274 - Personal Papers of Gordon C. Moore,1945. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Lot 615450 - Personal Papers of Mollye Brown,1908-1956. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Lot 619228 - Personal Papers of Patricia W. Allen,1961. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Lot 620723 - Personal Papers of Milton L. Raphael, Jr,1971-1975. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Lot 623395 - Personal Papers of J. Catherine Crokeron,1945-1962. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Lot 628323 - Personal Papers of William R. Brown,1924. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Lot 630089 - Personal Papers of Vera A. Dean,1942-1944. (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Lot 643074 - Personal Papers of Carl W. Hawkins,1925-1926. (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Lot 648104 - Personal Papers of Curtis L. Curling,1937-1951. (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Lot 658652 - Personal Papers of Carrie E. Copeland,1924-1926. (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Lot 668609 - Personal Papers of Thomas J. Maciborski,1960. (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Lot 671658 - Personal Papers of Paul A. Tatem,1906-1919. (1 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Lot 671658 - Personal Papers of Paul A. Tatem,1906-1919. (2 of 2) (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Lot 683861 - Personal Papers of J. M. Robertson,1889-1907. (1 of 3) (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Lot 683861 - Personal Papers of J. M. Robertson,1889-1907. (2 of 3) (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Lot 683861 - Personal Papers of J. M. Robertson,1887-1907. (3 of 3) (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Lot 696856 - Personal Papers of Gerald G. Gentry,1941-1943. (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Lot 708959 - Personal Papers of D. D. Dudley,1974. (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Lot 734473 - Personal Papers of W. F. Hobart,1938. (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Lot 738357 - Personal Papers of Joseph A. Markel,1912-1917. (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Lot 754656 - Personal Papers of Richard Hopkins,1964-1966. (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Lot 756576 - Personal Papers of E. W. Yawn,1947-1949. (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - Lot 759193 - Personal Papers of James O. Horn,1966. (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Lot 761909 - Personal Papers of the Cooper Family,1938-1970. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Lot 767968 - Personal Papers of Arthur Lee Smith,1967-1971. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Lot 770416 - Personal Papers of Robert H. Nitchie,1967. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Lot 774560 - Personal Papers of Theodore R. Harris,1967. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Lot 778548 - Personal Papers of Sharon M. Jone,1972. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Lot 779881 - Personal Papers of Jerry M. Skaggs,1961. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Lot 784292 - Personal Papers of Stanley Friedenberg,1956-1957. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Lot 784332 - Personal Papers of the Faltz Family,1953-1959. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Lot 790549 - Personal Papers of Daniel Clarence Smith,1924. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Lot 797083 - Personal Papers of William F. Morrison,1936-1945. (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Lot 816961 - Personal Papers of George W. Stavro,1861-1911. (1 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Lot 816961 - Personal Papers of George W. Stavro,1861-1911. (2 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Lot 827004 - Personal Papers of Peter Z. Kregloh,1965-1967. (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Lot 829550 - Personal Papers of David W. Darden,1919-1922. (1 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Lot 829550 - Personal Papers of David W. Darden,1919-1922. (2 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Lot 833794 - Personal Papers of Frank S. Moore,1966-1967. (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Lot 836831 - Personal Papers of W. R. Tompkins, Jr.,1829-1872. (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Lot 850197 - Personal Papers of Samuel Fambro,1941-1958. (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Lot 864342 - Personal Papers of Glenice Davis,1893-1912. (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Lot 866196 - Personal Papers of Mary T. Hite,1953-1959. (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Lot 892597 - Personal Papers of Janice W. Davis,1930. (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Lot 916071 - Personal Papers of Mary M. McCarty,1953. (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Lot 917963 - Personal Papers of Sarah G. Ore,1918-1970. (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Lot 929817 - Personal Papers of Durham St. Logan Waller,1951-1955. (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Lot 945366 - Personal Papers of Walter K. Deal,1912-1916. (Box 30, Folder 25)